<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News (en) &#8211; LFWF Pro Students Assignment</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 06:06:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8</generator>

<image>
	<url>./../../../wp-content/uploads/2021/07/logo-client-1-150x131.jpg</url>
	<title>News (en) &#8211; LFWF Pro Students Assignment</title>
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The school will also be closed in September.</title>
		<link>./../../../2020/08/26/the%20school%20will%20also%20be%20closed%20in%20september/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2020/08/26/the%20school%20will%20also%20be%20closed%20in%20september/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[MD Zahirul Islam]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News (en)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#160; The holiday of the school is being extended till September due to the lack of open environment. September will be the whole month of the holiday in the school. In addition to conducting classes on Parliament TV and radio, online platform learning will be conducted to keep the lessons running. Senior Secretary of the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p>
<div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><a href="Zahir360.blogspot.com.jpg" style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"><img loading="lazy" alt="Never stop learning" border="0" data-original-height="1242" data-original-width="1920" height="414" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2020/08/2761394_L.jpg" title="Never stop learning" width="640" /></a></div>
<p><span><!-- more --></span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The <b>holiday</b> of the school is being extended till September due to the lack of open environment. September will be the whole month of the holiday in the school. In addition to conducting classes on Parliament TV and radio, online platform learning will be conducted to keep the lessons running. Senior Secretary of the Ministry of Primary and Public <b>Education</b>, Mo. Akram-al-Hussein.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">According to the sources, the Ministry of Education and the Ministry of Primary and Public Education will discuss and decide on extending the holiday in the school by Thursday. Both ministries have decided in principle that the school will not be open in September.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Dr. Singh, <b>education minister</b>, has said that the government will not be able to open the school <b>Dipu Moni </b>has reported multiple times that the atmosphere was not enough to open the school in September. The media will be informed about the opening of the school if the open environment is open. &#8216;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">When asked about the opening of the school in September, the Minister of<b> Primary and Public Education,</b> Mo. &#8220;There is no environment to open the school,&#8221; Zakir Hossain told reporters. We are determined not to let future generations be destroyed. &#8216;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Senior Secretary of the Ministry of Primary and Public Education, Mo. Akram Al-Hussein told the Bangla Tribune that there was no atmosphere to open the school in September. We have targeted October and November, we will not open the school in September. &#8216;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The senior secretary added, &#8220;I asked the National Academy of Elementary Education (NEP) to plan three alternative lessons. Three plans were asked for September, October and November. Since the september is not yet ready to open, I&#8217;m not going to miss September. The lesson plan is designed to be forwarded in October and November. &#8216;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The Secretary said that the Ministry of Education and the Ministry of Primary and Public Education will sit together and decide on the holiday of the school. A decision will be taken by next Thursday. &#8216;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Since March 8, all the schools in the country have been closed since March 17 after the first ever corona patient was detected. The government has announced a holiday in the district till August 31. In addition to conducting classes on Parliament TV and radio, online reading will be conducted to keep the lessons going during the bandh.</p>
<p><span><span id="more-294"></span></span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2020/08/26/the%20school%20will%20also%20be%20closed%20in%20september/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Primary education is not being tested.</title>
		<link>./../../../2020/08/26/primary-education-is-not-being-tested/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2020/08/26/primary-education-is-not-being-tested/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[MD Zahirul Islam]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 04:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News (bn)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News (en)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Primary education is not being tested.&#160; This year, the fifth grade primary education examination (PEC) is not being held. Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina has agreed to this. This information was received from the Ministry of Primary and Public Education on Tuesday afternoon. This decision was taken in the case of the coronavirus. Senior Secretary of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;" trbidi="on">
<div style="text-align: justify;">
<div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;">
<a href="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-hv4Oluf-byE/X0XVxmDFkEI/AAAAAAAABWE/Uo40fzg0YwYAAFXvub7KOxQVzdJYXyN3ACLcBGAsYHQ/s1600/286245_L.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="clear: left; float: left; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-right: 1em;"><img loading="lazy" border="0" data-original-height="1067" data-original-width="1600" height="213" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2020/08/286245_L.jpg" width="320" /></a></div>
<p></div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
<br />
<!-- more --></div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
<h2>
Primary education is not being tested.&nbsp;</h2>
<div>
</div>
<p>This year, the fifth grade primary education examination (PEC) is not being held. Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina has agreed to this. This information was received from the Ministry of Primary and Public Education on Tuesday afternoon. This decision was taken in the case of the coronavirus.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
Senior Secretary of the Ministry of Primary and Public Education, Mo. We sent a summary of the PEC proposal; It&#8217;s agreed. The necessary action will be taken.</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
<h2>
<b>প্রাথমিক শিক্ষা পরীক্ষা করা হচ্ছে না।</b></h2>
<div>
<b><br /></b></div>
<p>এ বছর পঞ্চম শ্রেণীর প্রাথমিক শিক্ষা পরীক্ষা (পিইসি) অনুষ্ঠিত হচ্ছে না। প্রধানমন্ত্রী শেখ হাসিনা এতে সম্মত হয়েছেন। মঙ্গলবার বিকেলে প্রাথমিক ও গণশিক্ষা মন্ত্রণালয় থেকে এ তথ্য পাওয়া যায়। করোনাভাইরাসের ক্ষেত্রে এই সিদ্ধান্ত নেওয়া হয়।</p>
<h2>
<b></b></h2>
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
প্রাথমিক ও গণশিক্ষা মন্ত্রণালয়ের সিনিয়র সচিব মো. আমরা পিইসি প্রস্তাবের একটি সারসংক্ষেপ পাঠিয়েছি; এটা একমত। প্রয়োজনীয় ব্যবস্থা নেওয়া হবে।</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2020/08/26/primary-education-is-not-being-tested/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The decision to extend the holiday in the school!</title>
		<link>./../../../2020/08/26/the-general-holiday-in-city/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2020/08/26/the-general-holiday-in-city/index.html#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[MD Zahirul Islam]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News (en)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false"></guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The decision to extend the holiday in the school! The general holiday in the city of Saind ends on August 31. The holiday period may be extended further. This information was received from the Department of Secondary and Higher Education and the Ministry of Primary and Public Education on Monday. Sources said the government has [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;" trbidi="on">
<div style="text-align: justify;">
<h2 style="text-align: center;">
The decision to extend the holiday in the school!</h2>
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
<table align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" class="tr-caption-container" style="float: left; margin-right: 1em; text-align: left;">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-kcxHYgFPwCc/X0XRn96bZCI/AAAAAAAABVo/EMMaxafT29Ejd8SQQzUu9V6QVGiZB1EwgCLcBGAsYHQ/s1600/1093758_L.jpg" imageanchor="1" style="margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><img loading="lazy" alt="The decision to extend the holiday in the school!" border="0" data-original-height="1067" data-original-width="1600" height="213" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2020/08/1093758_L.jpg" title="The decision to extend the holiday in the school!" width="320" /></a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="tr-caption" style="text-align: center;"></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><b></b><br />
<!-- more --><b><br /></b></div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
<b><br /></b></div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
<b>The general holiday </b>in the city of Saind ends on August 31. The holiday period may be extended further. This information was received from the Department of Secondary and Higher Education and the Ministry of Primary and Public Education on Monday.</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
Sources said the <b>government</b> has decided in principle that the country&#8217;s epidemic of the coronavirus situation is not normal. The announcement is likely to come on Tuesday. The decision will allow for a fresh 15-day holiday.</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
On Monday, an additional secretary of the Department of Secondary and Higher Education said that the school is on leave till August 31. But the policy decision to extend the holiday was taken in the absence of the situation in <b>Corona</b>. The meeting of the divisional heads including the <b>Education Minister, Education Minister</b>, Secretary of Secondary and Higher Education and Technical and Madras department was held.</p>
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
<b>English Medium School Dhaka.&nbsp;</b></div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
Announcement of holiday in the state</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
Earlier on Sunday, Senior Secretary of the Ministry of Primary and Public Education, Mo. Akram Al-Hussein said that the Education Minister said that there is no environment for opening the school. Everyone understands this. Moreover, it is not possible to risk parents and children by opening schools.</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
</div>
<div style="text-align: justify;">
He said that it would be better not to put children at risk because of the situation. The decision will be taken after consultation with the <b>government</b> on opening the school.</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2020/08/26/the-general-holiday-in-city/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
